export const flashcards = [
  {
    front: 'Risk',
    back:
      'an uncertain event or condition that, if it occurs, has a positive or negative effect on one or more project objectives such as the scope, schedule, cost, and quality.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Management',
    back:
      'a systematic process of identifying, analyzing, and responding to project risks.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Management Plan',
    back:
      'articulates the progressions, instruments, measures and procedures that will be utilized to manage and administer those events that have the potential to cause a negative impact on the project’s outcome',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Categories',
    back:
      'lists of common areas or sources of risk experienced by the company, or on similar projects.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Probability',
    back: 'describes the potential for the risk event occurring.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Impact',
    back:
      "describes the effects or consequences the project will experience if the risk event occurs. The impact may be in terms of money, time, organization's reputation, loss of business, injury to people, damage to property and so on.",
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Breakdown Structures',
    back:
      'A hierarchically organised depiction of the identified project risks arranged by category.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Failure Mode and Effects Analysis (FMEA)',
    back:
      'the process of reviewing as many components, assemblies, and subsystems as possible to identify potential failure modes in a system and their causes and effects.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Analysis',
    back:
      'examining how project outcomes and objectives might change due to the impact of the risk event. It aims to prioritize the identified risks by measuring risk severity, often referred to as exposure.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Probability and Impact Assessment',
    back:
      'the process of assessing the probabilities and consequences of risk events if they are realized. The results of this assessment are then used to prioritize risks to establish a most-to-least-critical importance ranking.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Register',
    back:
      'is a document used as a risk management tool and to fulfill regulatory compliance acting as a repository for all risks identified and includes additional information about each risk, e.g. nature of the risk, mitigation measures. It can be displayed as a scatterplot or as a table',
  },
  {
    front: 'Qualitative Risk Analysis',
    back:
      'The process of prioritizing risks for further analysis or action by assessing and combining their probability of occurrence and impact. It considers all the risks identified in the identify risk process. It uses stakeholders inputs (expert judgment) to judge the likelihood and impact.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Quantitative Analysis',
    back:
      'The process of numerically analyzing the effect of identified risks on overall project objectives. It only considers the risks which we mark for further analysis in the Qualitative Analysis stage as these are the risks that have a high impact on the project objectives. It uses the probability distributions to characterize the risk’s probability and impact. It also uses the project model (e.g., schedule, cost estimate), mathematical and simulation tools to calculate the probability and impact.It predicts likely project outcomes in terms of money or time based on combined effects of risks. It also estimates the likelihood of meeting targets and communicates contingency needed to achieve the desired level of comfort.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Assumption Log',
    back:
      'a document which the project manager and team use to capture, document, and track assumptions and constraints about the product, project, environment, stakeholders, and other factors that can influence the project and product scope.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Avoiding Risk',
    back:
      'Risk avoidance is a risk response strategy whereby the project team acts to eliminate the threat or protect the project from its impact. It usually involves changing the project management plan to eliminate the threat entirely',
  },
  {
    front: 'Reducing Risk',
    back:
      'a risk response strategy whereby the project team acts to reduce the probability of occurrence or impact of a risk. It implies a reduction in the probability and/or impact of an adverse risk to be within acceptable threshold limits.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Transferring Risk',
    back:
      'Risk transference is a risk response strategy whereby the project team  shifts the impact of a threat to a third party, together with ownership of the response. Transferring the risk simply gives another party responsibility for its management—it does not eliminate it.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Accepting Risk',
    back:
      'a risk response strategy whereby the project team decides to acknowledge the risk and not take any action unless the risk occurs. This strategy is adopted where it is not possible or cost-effective to address a specific risk in any other way',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Audits',
    back:
      'examine and document the effectiveness of risk responses in dealing with identified risks and their root causes, as well as the effectiveness of the risk management process. The project manager is responsible for ensuring that risk audits are performed at an appropriate frequency, as defined in the project’s risk management plan.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Value and Trend Analysis',
    back:
      'is the quantitative investigation of the difference between actual and planned behavior. This technique is used for determining the cause and degree of difference between the baseline and actual performance and to maintain control over a project.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Contingency Planning',
    back:
      'Making a response plan that will only be executed under certain predefined conditions, if it is believed that there will be sufficient warning to implement the plan.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Identify Risk',
    back:
      'The process of determining which risks may affect the project and documenting their characteristics.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Control Risk',
    back:
      'the process of implementing risk response plans, tracking identified risks, monitoring residual risks, identifying new risks, and evaluating risk process effectiveness throughout the project.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Agile',
    back:
      'Agile practices approach discovering requirements and developing solutions through the collaborative effort of self-organizing and cross-functional teams and their customer(s)/end user(s). It advocates adaptive planning, evolutionary development, early delivery, and continual improvement, and it encourages flexible responses to change.',
  },
  {
    front: 'SCRUM',
    back:
      'a framework for project management that emphasizes teamwork, accountability and iterative progress toward a well-defined goal.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Cause and Effect Diagram',
    back:
      'a tool that helps identify, sort, and display possible causes of a specific problem or quality characteristic. It graphically illustrates the relationship between a given outcome and all the factors that influence the outcome.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Assumption Analysis',
    back:
      'a technique that explores the accuracy of assumptions and identifies risks to the project from inaccuracy, inconsistency, or incompleteness of assumptions. During this process, it may be deemed that the assumption is valid and worth any perceived risk or, in some cases, it may be determined that an assumption is in fact not valid, and an alternate course of action may be recommended and/or implemented outright',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Data Quality Assessment',
    back:
      'a project management technique that is used to evaluate the level or degree to which data about risks is necessary for risk management. It also looks into the accuracy, reliability, quality and integrity of the data concerning the risk.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Risk Urgency Assessment',
    back:
      'a project management process that reviews and determines the timing of actions that need to happen sooner than the other risk items.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Sensitivity Analysis',
    back:
      'The sensitivity analysis is a modeling technique that determines which risks have the most impact on the project. As one of the tools used in sensitivity analysis, the tornado diagram is used to compare the importance (relative) of different variables.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Tornado Diagram',
    back:
      'a type of sensitivity chart where the variable with the highest impact is placed at the top of the chart followed by other variables in descending impact order.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Monetary Value Analysis',
    back:
      'a statistical concept that calculates the average outcome when the future includes scenarios that may or may not happen. An EMV analysis is usually mapped out using a decision tree to represent the different options or scenarios.',
  },
  {
    front: 'Lean Management',
    back:
      'is an approach to managing an organization that supports the concept of continuous improvement, a long-term approach to work that systematically seeks to achieve small, incremental changes in processes in order to improve efficiency and quality.',
  },
];
